Gergő Buglyó

Front-end developer

Personal details

Name Gergő Buglyó

Email address gergobuglyo@gmail.com

Phone number +3630/501-2959

Linkedin linkedin.com/in/gergobuglyo

Portfolio gergobuglyo.com

A Self-taught Front-end Programmer who is motivated to learn new skills and take on new challenges at the next level of his web development carrier.

I started my career as a civil engineer. About two years ago, I decided to take a new direction in my career, I started my learning journey in web development. I acquired the basic tools of web development through my own projects, such as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and I've done some projects with React. Projects in the "Technical Projects" section helped me to strengthen and enhance my knowledge.

Skills

HTLM | CSS | Bootstrap | Tailwind CSS | JavaScript | React | NodeJS | WebRTC | Express | MongoDB

Technical Projects

Random user generator

An application that allows its users to generate random users with filters. Built using HTML, Bootstrap, React and randomuser.me API.

Skype clone application

Skype clone application, to create a connection between two users. Built using <u>HTML</u>, <u>CSS</u>, <u>React</u>, <u>NodeJS</u>, <u>Express</u>, <u>WebRTC</u>.

Mastermind game

Code-breaking game in a web application. Built using <u>HTML</u>, <u>CSS</u>, <u>JavaScript</u>.

Trivia quiz application

Simple multiple-choice quiz application. Built using <u>React</u>, <u>Tailwind CSS</u>, <u>TypeScript</u> and trivia quiz <u>API</u>.

Car list Rest API

Simple Rest API project. There are three branches. First version used plain NodeJS. In the enhanced version the express framework was implemented and finally the database was stored in the MongoDB database. Built using NodeJS, Express, MongoDB.

Education

2021 -2022	Online Web Development Bootcamp Programozaskarrier.hu – bootcamp and mentoring programme with high quality mentors
2016 - 2017	Pannon Education Center Secondary degree, Occupational Safety and Health Technology
2009 - 2014	University of Pécs Faculty of Engineering and Informatic Technology Bachelor of Engineering, Graduated as a Civil Engineer

Employment

Throughout my career and studies as a civil engineer, I have learned the basics of engineering thinking and I've picked up some useful skills that I can use in my future career as a web developer, such as: working independently and in a team, agility, responsibility and perseverance.

2023 – current	Freelancer Produce content (videos, articles) for the <u>Progr</u> mentor new students.	Web Developer amozás Karrier program and help
	Creating websites for small businesses.	
2018 – current	Rekontir Group Estimate of the money required to undertake a construction project. Developing and implementing construction budget accounting processes. Create complex excel spreadsheets, work with a huge database.	
2017 - 2018	Aktuál Bau Kft. Taking responsibility for the day-to-day on site Maintaining communication with customers an	
2017 - 2017	2G Building Kft Responsible for the day-to-day on site running Maintaining communication with customers an	
2016 - 2017	Allinferr Média Kft Managing a complete construction project fron	Project Manager n design to implementation.
2015 - 2016	McDonald's, London Worked in London to start learning English.	Employee

Language competencies

English – advanced mid Hungarian - native